Brien Barr

1046 Churchill Ct., Carmel, IN 46280 | Email: barrdom@hotmail.com | Phone: 317-910-6049 LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/p-brien-barr-587ba8164 | GitHub: https://github.com/BrienBarr

Summary

Experienced full stack developer with over 3 years experience creating interactive programs for museums and science centers. Over 10 years front end development experience with creating and maintaining corporate site. Adept in and executing strategies to complete projects on time and within budget. Works well in both a team and individual environment.

Technical Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- jQueryAPI
- Node.js
- PHP
- Visual Studio Code

- GitHub
- Windows OS
- Microsoft Office 365
- Adobe Production Software (Premiere, Photoshop, After Effects, Dreamweaver, InDesign)
- Autodesk 3ds Max
- Autodesk AutoCAD LT

Projects

- Database Interactive touchscreen interactive app using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, and DataTables JavaScript library to allow user to sort and browse history of police officers killed in the line of duty.
 - Links not available.
- What's for Dinner? interactive app allowing user to search for and save meal and cocktail recipes while getting a random joke using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, local storage, and API calls. Deployed application: https://devoyno.github.io/food drinks jokes/ GitHub repository: https://github.com/Devoyno/food drinks jokes
- Weather Dashboard interactive app allowing user to search for cities or recall from search history to get current weather and 5-day forecast using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, local storage, and API calls.

Deployed application: https://brienbarr.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/ GitHub repository: https://github.com/BrienBarr/Weather-Dashboard

Experience

Bowen Technovation (2002-Present)

7999 East 88th Street, Indianapolis, IN 46280 317-863-0525

2017-Present

Full stack interactive developer - responsible for creating and deploying user interactive experiences for museums and science centers

Brien Barr (Continued)

1046 Churchill Ct., Carmel, IN 46280 | Email: <u>barrdom@hotmail.com</u> | Phone: 317-910-6049 LinkedIn: <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/p-brien-barr-587ba8164</u> | GitHub: <u>https://github.com/BrienBarr</u>

Experience (Continued)

2003-Present

Website Creation and Maintenance - in charge of creating web content and maintaining corporate website IT and Computer Maintenance - maintained all in-house computers, network, and printers Graphic Layout/Design for Print and Web - created marketing materials for print and web Content Production Manager - managed all audio/video/interactive content creation and deployment

2002-2003

Assistant Audio/Video Editor - assisted with all audio and video content editing

Education

Butler Executive Coding Bootcamp - Indianapolis, IN 46208 Certificate

The Recording Workshop - Chillicothe, OH 45601

Certificate - Recording Engineering and Music Production Program

Certificate - Studio Maintenance and Troubleshooting Program

Certificate - Advanced Recording Engineering and Music Production Program

Certificate - New Technology Production Program

Ball State University - Muncie, IN 47306

Graduated Magna Cum Laude

BA Telecommunications/Production Minor in Film Studies